https://hippopress.com/terms-of-service/

Published Weekly
Dear readers,
Now more than ever Hippo depends on your support to help fund our coverage. Please consider supporting our local food, music, arts, pop culture and news coverage by becoming a sustaining member. Our staff is hard at work making your contributions count.
Thank you and we are truly grateful for your support.
Contribute Now
Become a member!
Login
About The Hippo
How To Contact Us
Advertising
Subscribe to the Hippo’s Long Weekend!
Find the Hippo – Map!
Terms of Service
HippoPress LLC (referred to as us or we) is New Hampshire based publishing company. We operate the website www.hippopress.com (Website).
These are the Terms and Conditions which govern each use you make of the membership payment services provided through the Website. These membership payments are intended to support the mission of HippoPress LLC.
These Terms and Conditions apply separately to each single payment that you make. By confirming on the Website that you wish to make a payment you agree to be bound by these Terms and Conditions for that payment.
(1) The payment services
We will use your payment at our discretion but within our stated company objectives.
All payments through the Website are to be made by payment card or via another agreed upon payment meathod.
Once you confirm to us through the Website that you wish to proceed with your payment your transaction will be processed through our payment services provider, Stripe. By confirming that you wish to proceed with your donation you authorize Stripe to request funds from your credit, debit, or PayPal card provider.
(2) Unauthorised card use
If you become aware of fraudulent use of your card, or if it is lost or stolen, you must notify your card provider.
(4) Information from you
Before we can process a payment you must provide us with (i) your name, address and email address; and (ii) details of the credit or debit card that you wish to use to fund the payment. We will use this information to process your payment. It is your responsibility to ensure you have provided us with the correct information.
When you submit your payment details, these details will be transferred to our payment provider, Stripe, and your payment data will be collected and processed securely by them. You should make sure that you are aware of Stripe’s terms and conditions, which are different from our own, to ensure that you are comfortable with how they will process your personal data before you make a payment.
We won’t share your personal details with any other third party other than is set out in our Privacy Policy. Our Privacy Policy forms part of these Payment Terms and Conditions and by agreeing to these Terms and Conditions you are also agreeing to the way we use and protect your personal information in line with our Privacy Policy.
(5) Refund policy
If you make an error in your donation please contact us either by email at sales@hippopress.com, by phone at 603-625-1855, extension 150, or my mail at HippoPress LLC, 195 McGregor Street, Unit 325, Manchester, NH 03102. Payments are not refundable after 30 days.
(6) Your payments are a NON-DEDUCTABLE donation to a for-profit company, HippoPress LLC, to support our mission of producing a periodical. Payments to us to not constitute an agreement for us to provide goods or services to you. Any item of value, including but not limited to membership, thank you gifts, discounts and other services and or goods provided to you or offered to you have no monetary value. If for some reason HippoPress LLC cannot or does not provide these items you agree to not seek a refund. None will be provided.
(7) General
We reserve the right to amend these Payment Terms and Conditions at any time.
These Payment Terms and Conditions are governed by New Hampshire law and are subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the New Hampshire courts.
LIMITATION OF LIABILITY
YOU AGREE THAT UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES SHALL WE BE LIABLE FOR DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL, PUNITIVE, EXEMPLARY, OR ANY OTHER DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF YOUR USE OF THE SITE OR SERVICE. ADDITIONALLY, HIPPOPRESS LLC IS NOT LIABLE FOR DAMAGES IN CONNECTION WITH (I) ANY FAILURE OF PERFORMANCE, ERROR, OMISSION, DENIAL OF SERVICE, ATTACK, INTERRUPTION, DELETION, DEFECT, DELAY IN OPERATION OR TRANSMISSION, COMPUTER VIRUS, OR LINE OR SYSTEM FAILURE; (II) LOSS OF REVENUE, ANTICIPATED PROFITS, BUSINESS, SAVINGS, GOODWILL OR DATA; AND (III) THIRD PARTY THEFT OF, DESTRUCTION OF, UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO, ALTERATION OF, OR USE OF YOUR INFORMATION OR PROPERTY, REGARDLESS OF OUR NEGLIGENCE, GROSS NEGLIGENCE, FAILURE OF AN ESSENTIAL PURPOSE AND WHETHER SUCH LIABILITY ARISES IN NEGLIGENCE, CONTRACT, TORT, OR ANY OTHER THEORY OF LEGAL LIABILITY. THE FOREGOING APPLIES EVEN IF WE HIPPOPRESS LLC HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF OR COULD HAVE FORESEEN THE DAMAGES. IN THOSE STATES THAT DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR THE DAMAGES, OUR LIABILITY IS LIMITED TO THE FULLEST POSSIBLE EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW.
Holiday Meal Dining Out
Holiday Meal Take Out
Looking for more? Become a member and log in!
Log in to view your:You are not currently logged in.Username or Email Address:Password: Remember Me» Register» Lost your Password?More from the Hippo Shop Hippo
Write To Us
Hippo Best Of 2020
Read by Interest! FREE to Read!
Thanks to Member Support
Art & Theatre
Cover Stories
Family Fun
Food
Outdoors
Music & Comedy
News
Pop Culture
Log in to view your:You are not currently logged in.Username or Email Address:Password: Remember Me» Register» Lost your Password?CategoriesCategories
Select Category
Albums
Art & Theater
Best Of
Best of 2020
Books
Comedy
Cover Stories
Copyright © 2020 — The Hippo Press. All Rights Reserved.
Terms of Service
